Great, great.
Thanks to this hero.
Great martial arts skills.
Really impressive.
What great skills.
Indeed.
You ignored the drowning child,
and dragged me, the rescuer, ashore instead.
What are your intentions?
Jingxuan.
Jingxuan, I found out.
The girl's surname is Tang.
She is a pipa instructor at the Jiaofangsi.
You just returned from your patrol
and haven't reported back yet.
If you break into the Jiaofangsi now,
aren't you giving Prince Yu leverage against you?
Don't worry, I'll have someone keep an eye on her.
She won't get away.
I have my own plans.
His Majesty's verbal decree.
Prince Shuo has rendered meritorious service in inspecting river affairs.
A music troupe from the Jiaofangsi is granted to enter his mansion.
Respect this.
My goodness.
Miss Tang,
your room is over here.
Please follow me.
Your Highness, Miss Tang has been settled.
Understood.
Your Highness, I don't know if I should say this.
Right? You also think they look alike, don't you?
It's not that they look alike.
She is her.
You may leave.
Yes, Your Highness.
The furnishings in this room are elegant and luxurious.
It shouldn't be a place for me to live, right?
Your Highness.
This servant didn't know it was Your Highness.
I have offended you.
Please forgive me.
This servant kowtows to you.
Tang Zhiluo,
why are you pretending not to know me?
When did Your Highness go to the Jiaofangsi?
How were your eyes cured?
Where is the scar?
Even if you want to pretend not to know me,
you don't have to go this far.
It's clearly Your Highness who is making things difficult for this servant.
'This servant'?
You were never this humble before.
This servant only met Your Highness once by the river.
I dare not claim any connection.
Tang Zhiluo, I've been looking for you for two whole years.
I don't care if you reincarnated or came back from the dead.
I don't care if you really don't remember or are just pretending.
I beg you,
don't ever leave me again.
Your Highness.
What is it?
Prince Yu is here.
Understood.
You will still live here from now on.
Since you left,
everything here has remained the same.
Let's go back to how we were,
okay?
We can't fight him head-on.
I'll be right back.
Prince Shuo is crazy and eccentric,
just as the rumors say.
I must find a way to leave the mansion.
Please wait, Miss Tang.
Miss Tang, I didn't expect your medical skills to be so excellent,
and your pipa playing to be so outstanding.
It's as delicate as pearls falling on a jade plate,
and as powerful as ten thousand galloping horses.
Wonderful.
You flatter me, sir.
Miss, this is our Prince Yu.
So it is the gentle and wise Third Prince.
I pay my respects to Prince Yu.
I didn't expect Your Highness to be so fond of music.
Miss Tang is my sixth brother's woman.
There's no need to be so polite to me.
Just call me Third Brother as he does.
What do you mean, Prince Yu?
I am just a humble musician.
How dare I presume to associate with Prince Shuo?
Your Highness, you know me?
Oh.
I see.
My sixth brother
is truly infatuated.
Why does Prince Yu know me?
The back door is also guarded.
Third Brother, you are rambling.
What exactly do you want to say?
Sixth Brother, you miss an old friend.
But new clothes are better,
and old friends are the best.
People who look alike in this world
are countless.
You can't take them all into your mansion.